scubadiverlife.com 2019-05-04

# Privacy Policy • Scuba Diver Life

Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to the ScubaDiverLife.com and Scuba Diver Life and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to Scuba Diver Life include ScubaDiverLife.com and SDL. The SDL website is a news and information site. By using the SDL website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

### Collection of your Personal Information

SDL may collect personally identifiable information, such as your name. We may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.

Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by SDL. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the SDL website.

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through SDL’s public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others.

SDL encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from SDL so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. SDL is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the SDL website.

### Use of your Personal Information

SDL collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested.

SDL may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from SDL and its affiliates. SDL may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

### SDL does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.

SDL may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. SDL may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to SDL, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

SDL will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on SDL or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of SDL; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of SDL, or the public.

### Use of Cookies

The SDL website may use “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize SDL pages, or register with SDL site or services, a cookie helps SDL to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same SDL website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the SDL features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the SDL services or websites you visit.

### Security of your Personal Information

SDL secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure.

### Children Under Thirteen

SDL does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.

### Opt-Out & Unsubscribe

We respect your privacy and give you an opportunity to opt-out of receiving announcements of certain information. Users may opt-out of receiving any or all communications from SDL by contacting us at: Admin@ScubaDiverLife.com

### Changes to this Statement

SDL will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. SDL encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how SDL is protecting your information.

### Contact Information

SDL welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy.  
If you believe that SDL has not adhered to this Statement, please contact SDL at:

Scuba Diver Life  
650 Castro St.  
Mountain View, California 94041  
Email Address:  
Admin@ScubaDiverLife.com  
Effective as of July 08, 2012
